{
    "id": "4ORbqlB4fcM",
    "title": "How fast is the Rasberry Pi 5 WiFi? #shorts #raspberrypi5 #wifi",
    "channel": "David Bombal",
    "channel_id": "UCP7WmQ_U4GB3K51Od9QvM0w",
    "subscriber_count": 2650000,
    "upload_date": "2023-10-03T15:30:01Z",
    "video_url": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4ORbqlB4fcM",
    "category": "People & Blogs",
    "tags": [
        "raspberry pi 5",
        "raspberrypi5",
        "raspberry pi",
        "raspberry pi 4",
        "wifi",
        "wi-fi",
        "pi 5",
        "pi5",
        "raspberry pi5",
        "wpa2",
        "wpa3",
        "wpa",
        "raspberry 5",
        "pi 5 vs pi 4",
        "linux",
        "wifi password",
        "password",
        "wireless",
        "ssid",
        "show wifi password",
        "find wifi password",
        "wlan",
        "wifi hacking",
        "cybersecurity",
        "hacking",
        "ethical hacking",
        "hacker",
        "wpa2 cracking",
        "wifi password hacker",
        "wpa2 hacking",
        "wifi cracking",
        "hack",
        "kali linux",
        "wifi gadget",
        "md5",
        "password cracking",
        "password crack",
        "md5 password",
        "sha",
        "sha1",
        "sha256",
        "sha512"
    ],
    "views": 67988,
    "likes": 2844,
    "comments_count": 28,
    "description": "Please note that I was not paid for this video. Raspberry Pi did send me a free Raspberry Pi 5 for me to test with.  #raspberrypi5 #raspberrypi4 #raspberrypi",
    "description_links": [],
    "transcript": "This is a Raspberry Pi 5. Let's test how good theWi-Fi is on a Raspberry Pi 5. Got the Raspberry Pi 5 connected to OBS on this laptop I've also got an application called iPERF running on the Mac the Raspberry Pi's IP address is 192.168.085 it doesn't have an Ethernet cable connected it's connected via Wi-Fi to this router. Now this is obviously not a great test because the Raspberry Pi right next to the router but it gives us an indication of possible speeds. The Mac is also connected to the same Wi-Fi network. So on the Raspberry Pi I'll use the command iperf3 -s because it's the server and as you can see it's listening on Port 5201 on the Mac we'll connect to that IP address on Port 5201 and I'll click start. Here we're getting 120 megabits per second. So on the Mac you can see we're getting about 126 megabits per second I have had it go faster kind of depends but here's a very unscientific test of the Wi-Fi on a Raspberry Pi 5",
    "transcript_keywords": [
        "Raspberry",
        "Mac",
        "connected",
        "Ethernet cable connected",
        "test",
        "WiFi",
        "Mac the Raspberry",
        "Port",
        "Ethernet cable",
        "router",
        "address",
        "connected to OBS",
        "OBS",
        "Ethernet",
        "megabits",
        "good theWiFi",
        "listening on Port",
        "cable connected",
        "great test",
        "address on Port"
    ],
    "transcript_entity_values": [
        "Port 5201",
        "IP",
        "the Raspberry Pi",
        "Mac",
        "the Wi-Fi",
        "Mac",
        "about 126 megabits",
        "120 megabits",
        "the Raspberry Pi's",
        "iperf3",
        "192.168.085",
        "-s",
        "Wi-Fi",
        "the Raspberry Pi"
    ],
    "transcript_entity_types": [
        "FAC",
        "ORG",
        "ORG",
        "PERSON",
        "ORG",
        "ORG",
        "QUANTITY",
        "QUANTITY",
        "ORG",
        "PERSON",
        "DATE",
        "PERSON",
        "LOC",
        "FAC"
    ]
}