{
    "id": "5yQxnD_4gWQ",
    "title": "Samsung Galaxy Home smart speaker with Bixby: first look",
    "channel": "The Verge",
    "channel_id": "UCddiUEpeqJcYeBxX1IVBKvQ",
    "subscriber_count": 3390000,
    "upload_date": "2018-08-09T18:54:20Z",
    "video_url": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5yQxnD_4gWQ",
    "category": "Science & Technology",
    "tags": [
        "samsung",
        "samsung galaxy",
        "bixby smart speaker",
        "bixby samsung",
        "bixby button",
        "samsung galaxy unpacked",
        "galaxy home",
        "home speaker",
        "samsung home",
        "Bixby 2.0",
        "siri vs bixby",
        "bixby assistant",
        "voice assistant",
        "smart assistant",
        "google assistant",
        "bixby",
        "assistant",
        "siri",
        "alexa",
        "echo",
        "google",
        "google home",
        "samsung mobile",
        "review",
        "hands-on",
        "first look",
        "technology",
        "top 10",
        "gadgets",
        "tech",
        "tech news",
        "latest updates",
        "mkbhd",
        "marques brownlee",
        "apple",
        "microsoft",
        "verge",
        "the verge",
        "need to know",
        "galaxy watch"
    ],
    "views": 198786,
    "likes": 2780,
    "comments_count": 259,
    "description": "Samsungs new Galaxy Home is a premium speaker with Bixby built in. Its a direct answer to the Apple HomePod, Amazon Echo, Google Home, Sonos One, and other smart speakers. But is Bixby really smart enough to put in your living room?  Subscribe:   Like The Verge on Facebook:  Follow on Twitter:  Follow on Instagram:  Read More:  Community guidelines:   Subscribe to Verge Science on YouTube, a new home base for our explorations into the future of science:",
    "description_links": [
        "http://goo.gl/G5RXGs",
        "https://goo.gl/2P1aGc",
        "https://goo.gl/XTWX61",
        "https://goo.gl/7ZeLvX",
        "http://www.theverge.com",
        "http://bit.ly/2D0hlAv",
        "http://bit.ly/2FqJZMl"
    ],
    "transcript": "- Hey it's Chris Welch with The Verge, here at Samsung's Unpacked Event in Brooklyn, New York, where we just saw a lot of stuff. We saw the Note 9, the new Galaxy Watch, and we got our first look at the long rumored Bixby speaker, which we now know is called Galaxy Home. So the speaker itself, the design is interesting. It's much bigger than any of its competitors. There are several speakers inside, really premium components, upscale sound. And there's fabric running around it. You've got rubberized touch buttons on top, a single power wire running into it. No Aux input, which is kind of disappointing to see from Samsung, the headphone jack company. So Samsung brought out Spotify CEO Daniel Ek on stage, and that's a long term partnership with the company. Apple has Apple Music for it's home pod. Amazon has a music service. But Samsung is gonna ride on Spotify for its speakers, its phones, its watches. It's even gonna put Spotify on Samsung's refrigerator. So Spotify is gonna be everywhere, it's gonna take awhile, but they're making this sound like a big deal. It's gonna last a long time. So just like Apple's homepod and the other speakers you can start listening to the music on your phone and send it over to the Galaxy Home and keep listening there. So Samsung spent a lot of time talking about Bixby, which has a bad rap compared to Siri and Google Assistant. The company is really trying to make it smarter, more capable. It's a hard hill to overcome, because by now Bixby's reputation might be pretty tarnished. We couldn't actually try or test out the speakers ourselves, but they brought out 160 Galaxy Home's and played them all at once, and that sounded pretty awesome. Hear it for yourself. - [Female Narrator] Hi Bixby. (dramatic music) - Besides that, we don't know many details or a price, or when this thing's coming out. Samsung just kinda brought it out, big ol' stage show, and said \"It's here, this is our speaker, coming soon.\" and kinda left it at that. Thanks for watching, stay tuned for our full review of the Galaxy Note 9, coming very soon and subscribe to The Verge on YouTube.",
    "transcript_keywords": [
        "Samsung Unpacked Event",
        "Event in Brooklyn",
        "Chris Welch",
        "Unpacked Event",
        "Samsung Unpacked",
        "Galaxy Home",
        "Samsung",
        "Galaxy",
        "Galaxy Watch",
        "Brooklyn",
        "York",
        "Chris",
        "Welch",
        "Unpacked",
        "Event",
        "called Galaxy Home",
        "Spotify",
        "Spotify CEO Daniel",
        "Home",
        "Bixby"
    ],
    "transcript_entity_values": [
        "New York",
        "The Verge on",
        "Apple",
        "Bixby",
        "Bixby",
        "Spotify",
        "Google",
        "YouTube",
        "Galaxy Home",
        "Samsung",
        "Amazon",
        "Galaxy Watch",
        "Chris Welch",
        "Brooklyn",
        "Siri",
        "Galaxy Home's",
        "first",
        "Daniel Ek",
        "160",
        "the Galaxy Home",
        "The Verge",
        "Apple Music"
    ],
    "transcript_entity_types": [
        "GPE",
        "ORG",
        "ORG",
        "GPE",
        "PERSON",
        "ORG",
        "ORG",
        "GPE",
        "ORG",
        "ORG",
        "ORG",
        "ORG",
        "PERSON",
        "GPE",
        "ORG",
        "ORG",
        "ORDINAL",
        "PERSON",
        "CARDINAL",
        "ORG",
        "ORG",
        "ORG"
    ]
}