{
    "id": "7qsY5--pOaY",
    "title": "8Bitdo Pro Controller Review",
    "channel": "This Does Not Compute",
    "channel_id": "UCEp20NgOZHmgWdbQdHSxgjw",
    "subscriber_count": 414000,
    "upload_date": "2017-11-27T16:00:01Z",
    "video_url": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7qsY5--pOaY",
    "category": "Science & Technology",
    "tags": [
        "8Bitdo",
        "controller",
        "video games",
        "SNES",
        "Super Nintendo",
        "Super Famicom",
        "Bluetooth",
        "Switch",
        "Windows",
        "macOS",
        "Android",
        "gaming",
        "mobile gaming",
        "smartphone",
        "gamepad",
        "review",
        "This Does Not Compute",
        "SN30 Pro",
        "SF30 Pro"
    ],
    "views": 75658,
    "likes": 2186,
    "comments_count": 263,
    "description": "Let's check out 8Bitdo's latest SNES-themed Bluetooth controller -- is it worth its pricetag?  8Bitdo SN30/SF30 Pro Controller product page:   -----------------------------------------------------------------------------  Please consider supporting my work on Patreon:   Follow me on Twitter and Instagram! @thisdoesnotcomp  TDNC t-shirts and apparel can be found at   This Does Not Compute PO Box 131141 St. Paul, MN 55113  -----------------------------------------------------------------------------  Music by Lakey Inspired ( Intro music by BoxCat Games (",
    "description_links": [
        "http://www.8bitdo.com/sn30pro-sf30pro/",
        "https://www.patreon.com/thisdoesnotcompute",
        "https://www.redbubble.com/people/thisdoesnotcomp",
        "http://www.soundcloud.com/lakeyinspired).",
        "http://www.box-cat.com)."
    ],
    "transcript": "Hey everyone, it's Colin. How's it goin'? Some people love the Nintendo Switch Joy-Con controllers. For those that don't, let's check out a new option with a retro look. [ Music - Intro ] This is the 8BitDo Pro controller. There are two models: the SF30 and SN30, and the only difference between 'em is the color scheme. Both were kindly sent my way by 8Bitdo for this review. The Pro controller is about the same size as the Super Famicom controller it resembles, though it's a bit heavier. The button action is quite good. It's very close to the original. Not too mushy, but also not clicky. It adds a pair of analog sticks, which are excellent. They're super smooth and have a nice texture to keep your thumbs from slipping off. The battery is rated for 16 hours of use and recharging takes about two hours. The controller has a USB Type-C port for this, and a cable is included in the box. You can use the controller in wired mode through that port as well, but most people will likely just go with Bluetooth. There are multiple profiles to choose from, based on which device you pair the controller to. They're selected by holding down a button combination while powering it on. This is a bit cumbersome, but at least 8BitDo has them printed on the back label. There are options for the Nintendo Switch, Android, Windows, and macOS, and the controller is compatible with Steam as well. Pairing is pretty quick, and since it uses Bluetooth 4.0, compatible devices can show the battery charge remaining. In a nod to the Switch, there are Home and Share buttons on the front, as that's a platform this controller seems primarily geared towards. The vibration motor isn't Nintendo's HD rumble variety, but it's smooth and pretty quiet. There's also an accelerometer for motion controls, but it lacks NFC, so there's no Amiibo support. The only real bummer with the Pro controller is that it's not compatible with iOS devices. One won't even see it when trying to pair. I'm told that this is intentional, and due to the cost of licensing for the MFi program. 8Bitdo sells an optional smartphone clip, and given the compact size of the controller, it could be a good option for mobile gaming. It's just too bad that iPhone users are left out. Overall, the 8Bitdo Pro Controller is a solid device. It has all the features of a modern gamepad with retro styling that doesn't affect its ergonomics. I'll admit its retail price of $50 US may seem a little high for a third-party controller. But if it saves you from having to buy separate controllers for each platform, then it very well could be the most economical option. I owe a big thank you to 8Bitdo for sending a pair of Pro Controllers my way to check out and review. I'll include a link down in the description. If you like the video, I'd appreciate a thumbs-up and be sure to subscribe if you haven't already. You can follow me on Twitter and Instagram at thisdoesnotcomp, and as always, thanks for watching.",
    "transcript_keywords": [
        "Pro controller",
        "controller",
        "Pro",
        "Colin",
        "Nintendo Switch",
        "Super Famicom controller",
        "Switch JoyCon controllers",
        "Nintendo Switch JoyCon",
        "Switch",
        "Nintendo",
        "pair",
        "Famicom controller",
        "option",
        "compatible",
        "Bluetooth",
        "Hey",
        "Super Famicom",
        "JoyCon controllers",
        "Super",
        "Switch JoyCon"
    ],
    "transcript_entity_values": [
        "Pro Controllers",
        "third",
        "Android",
        "about two hours",
        "the 8Bitdo Pro Controller",
        "Nintendo",
        "Super Famicom",
        "Amiibo",
        "Bluetooth",
        "two",
        "Instagram",
        "Switch",
        "16 hours",
        "$50 US",
        "Bluetooth 4.0",
        "8Bitdo",
        "One",
        "iPhone",
        "Colin",
        "NFC",
        "Twitter",
        "8Bitdo",
        "the Nintendo Switch"
    ],
    "transcript_entity_types": [
        "ORG",
        "ORDINAL",
        "ORG",
        "TIME",
        "ORG",
        "ORG",
        "ORG",
        "PERSON",
        "PERSON",
        "CARDINAL",
        "ORG",
        "ORG",
        "TIME",
        "MONEY",
        "ORG",
        "PERSON",
        "CARDINAL",
        "ORG",
        "PERSON",
        "ORG",
        "PERSON",
        "ORG",
        "ORG"
    ]
}