{
    "id": "GkWkQCsEYBE",
    "title": "Unboxing ALL 22 International Apple Watch Bands!",
    "channel": "iJustine",
    "channel_id": "UCey_c7U86mJGz1VJWH5CYPA",
    "subscriber_count": 7100000,
    "upload_date": "2021-07-15T17:21:40Z",
    "video_url": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GkWkQCsEYBE",
    "category": "Science & Technology",
    "tags": [
        "ijustine"
    ],
    "views": 285613,
    "likes": 11479,
    "comments_count": 2389,
    "description": "PLEASE SUBSCRIBE:  GET MY PINK iJUSTINE CABLES HERE:   GET MY EDITING PLUGIN:    MUSIC I USE -   FRIEND ME HERE:        MY NEW PROJECT:   PODCAST:       WHAT I USE TO MAKE VIDEOS    CAMERAS: Sony a7 IV -  Sony a1 -   Sony a7s III -   Insta 360 ONE X3 -  Insta 360 ONE RS -  Insta 360 GO2 -   LENSES: New Sony GM 24-70mm ii -  Older Sony GM 24-70mm -  New Sony Sony 20-70mm -  Sony GM 16-35mm -  Sony GM 50mm -  Sony GM 135mm -  Sony GM 85mm -   AUDIO:  Sennheiser AVX Digital Wireless -  Sony XLR Adapter -  Sony Hot Shoe Shotgun -  Tiny Sony Microphone -  DJI Mics -  Rode Podcaster Pro II -  Podcaster Mic -  Elgato Wave 3 Mic -   DRONES: DJI Mavic 3 -  DJI Mini 3 -  DJI Air 2S -   LIGHTING: Aputure 600d Pro -  Aputure Light Dome II -  Aputure Amaran 200d -  Aputure 35in Light Dome -  Aputure Lantern Softbox -   Sony CF Express A 160g + Card Reader-  Sony CF Express A 800g -     These links are affiliate and by using them youre helping out my channel! Thank you!     BECOME A CHANNEL MEMBER:",
    "description_links": [
        "http://www.youtube.com/subscription_center?add_user=ijustine",
        "https://geni.us/wnIN",
        "https://mvfx.co/mKeynote-with-iJustine",
        "http://share.epidemicsound.com/NNNGs",
        "http://twitter.com/ijustine",
        "http://instagram.com/ijustine",
        "http://facebook.com/ijustine",
        "https://tiktok.com/@ijustine",
        "https://snapchat.com/add/ijustine",
        "http://twitter.com/jpig",
        "http://youtube.com/samebrain",
        "https://geni.us/U70407",
        "https://amzn.to/3jScz3h",
        "https://geni.us/mAtruYL",
        "https://geni.us/2mPGn",
        "https://geni.us/8kJHun",
        "https://geni.us/cZGA6ST",
        "https://geni.us/liSjf",
        "https://amzn.to/3DWqJau",
        "https://geni.us/irEgHq",
        "https://geni.us/vwolf",
        "https://geni.us/gxDS",
        "https://geni.us/R46usnU",
        "https://geni.us/diFZAJ",
        "https://geni.us/eaUR",
        "https://geni.us/TfEu",
        "https://geni.us/eqim0",
        "https://geni.us/hjmjD",
        "https://geni.us/pxN9Vw6",
        "https://geni.us/OmAta4o",
        "https://geni.us/6KKHkB",
        "https://geni.us/DXX7",
        "https://geni.us/RU6m",
        "https://geni.us/Ga4H",
        "https://geni.us/RaBW61",
        "https://geni.us/uKRvYQ",
        "https://geni.us/M1MUS",
        "https://geni.us/8I5a",
        "https://geni.us/DOJNEo",
        "https://geni.us/0b4zBFR",
        "https://geni.us/Gku22",
        "https://geni.us/p3RtyR",
        "https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCey_c7U86mJGz1VJWH5CYPA/join"
    ],
    "transcript": "- Hey, guys. It's Justine. And in front of me, I have 22 watch bands, representing 22 different countries. They released these in honor of the Tokyo Summer Olympics. And I'm so excited to unbox them because they all look so great. So, let's get started. (upbeat music) I love the gold detailing that they have on the Apple Watch logo. You're gonna see it, it's reflective. (upbeat music continues) Oh, there's even some gold detail right here. I love it. It's reflective and beautiful. Check that out. USA all the way, look at this. So to get the corresponding Apple Watch face, you just have to scan this app clip and that'll give you the corresponding watch face for each watch band. There's a lot of watch bands here. Sport loop bands are my favorite. I do love the solo loop, (snapping) but there's just something about this, that just feels so great. And it's easily adjustable unlike these ones where you do have to know what size you want. You've got a little detail right here. This little USA written right there on the inside. This is nice. Oh, I'm so excited. Let's scan this app clip. This stripe matches your new band. Look at this, here it is. Adding to my faces. I love that I can change the various styles. There's a full screen, there's a circular. You could change the stripe sizes? That's pretty great. One watch band down, only 21 left to go. And here's our South Africa watch bands. Look at this. (snapping) Great Britain. (snapping) Time for Italy! And here's Russia. Australia! There's still so many more to go. One, two, three, four, five, six. We still have 15 left. (laughs) Oh my god. And here's China. And here's the Netherlands. Time for France. Germany! And here's Greece. (snapping) (lively guitar music) Mexico! (sighs) This is the most exhausting thing that I've ever done, and I'm barely doing anything. Cool, Sweden. Canada! Here's Brazil. Time for New Zealand! South Korea. We have four more left. Next up, we have Belgium. Okay. We are officially out of room over here. So, I think we're gonna have to do this. Here's Japan! Time for Jamaica. And our last and final one, we have Denmark. And that is our last Apple watch band that we have to unbox here in the country edition of the international sport loops that Apple has released. These are so cool and I'm so glad they did this. I would love to know from you, guys, where are you from, what country you're from. And also, what is your favorite Olympic sport? Is there anyone that you're cheering for? Are you actually an Olympic athlete? Do you have friends or family that happened to be going to the Olympics or do you have future plans to become, maybe a potential future Olympian? I'd love to hear all of those and more in the comments below. And if you guys are new here, hello, welcome to my channel. I make a lot of fun tech videos. You guys can hit subscribe, it's free, and you can also hit the bell to be notified when I post new videos. And if you enjoyed this video, be sure to hit like, and I will see you guys in the next one. Now, the question is, which watch band am I gonna wear? I think New Zealand might be my favorite because it is the black and white aesthetic and I think it's beautiful. New Zealand, (finger snaps) gotcha. (upbeat music)",
    "transcript_keywords": [
        "watch",
        "Apple Watch",
        "watch band",
        "Tokyo Summer Olympics",
        "love",
        "Apple",
        "Apple watch band",
        "band",
        "Apple Watch face",
        "Tokyo Summer",
        "guys",
        "bands",
        "Time",
        "Zealand",
        "Apple Watch logo",
        "great",
        "Watch face",
        "Summer Olympics",
        "Africa watch bands",
        "South Africa watch"
    ],
    "transcript_entity_values": [
        "South Africa",
        "One",
        "Canada",
        "the next one",
        "Olympics",
        "Apple",
        "Justine",
        "Russia",
        "Mexico",
        "Olympian",
        "Time",
        "three",
        "Brazil",
        "Great Britain",
        "22",
        "Denmark",
        "Jamaica",
        "Netherlands",
        "France",
        "four",
        "Sweden",
        "Japan",
        "Australia",
        "five",
        "Greece",
        "USA",
        "only 21",
        "China",
        "Belgium",
        "six",
        "two",
        "South Korea",
        "New Zealand",
        "Germany",
        "Apple Watch",
        "Italy",
        "the Tokyo Summer Olympics",
        "Olympic",
        "15"
    ],
    "transcript_entity_types": [
        "GPE",
        "CARDINAL",
        "GPE",
        "DATE",
        "EVENT",
        "ORG",
        "PERSON",
        "GPE",
        "GPE",
        "ORG",
        "ORG",
        "CARDINAL",
        "GPE",
        "GPE",
        "CARDINAL",
        "GPE",
        "GPE",
        "GPE",
        "GPE",
        "CARDINAL",
        "GPE",
        "GPE",
        "GPE",
        "DATE",
        "GPE",
        "GPE",
        "CARDINAL",
        "GPE",
        "GPE",
        "CARDINAL",
        "CARDINAL",
        "GPE",
        "GPE",
        "GPE",
        "ORG",
        "GPE",
        "EVENT",
        "EVENT",
        "CARDINAL"
    ]
}