{
    "id": "LNeAP32MFu8",
    "title": "How to quickly find MAC Addresses in Windows 11 (and change them) #shorts",
    "channel": "David Bombal",
    "channel_id": "UCP7WmQ_U4GB3K51Od9QvM0w",
    "subscriber_count": 2650000,
    "upload_date": "2023-09-07T16:00:16Z",
    "video_url": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LNeAP32MFu8",
    "category": "People & Blogs",
    "tags": [
        "mac",
        "mac address",
        "change mac address",
        "mac address changer",
        "mac spoofing",
        "address",
        "how to change mac address",
        "media access control",
        "what is mac address",
        "how to find mac address",
        "windows",
        "how mac address works",
        "wifi",
        "mac address vs ip address",
        "mac filtering",
        "mac adress spoofing",
        "mac spoofing trick",
        "internet",
        "mac changing",
        "hacking",
        "mac changer",
        "kali linux",
        "macchanger",
        "ethernet",
        "change mac address windows 10",
        "mac address spoofing",
        "networking",
        "mac address windows 10",
        "spoofing"
    ],
    "views": 65602,
    "likes": 3483,
    "comments_count": 31,
    "description": "Watch this video for details on how to change your Windows MAC address:  or by using Python:    #wifi #windows #mac",
    "description_links": [
        "https://youtu.be/V3Pcc8b_m0U",
        "https://youtu.be/ZIqvGmrw7Tw"
    ],
    "transcript": "Do you know that you can easily find the MAC address of a Windows computer by using the getmac command? So I can use the command getmac /v get verbose information, that now shows me the Wi-Fi network with the MAC Address of the Wi-Fi network as well as various other networks. These are VMware Virtual Networks there are the Mac addresses of the 2 VMware networks. I could do that by going to Network and Internet Settings as an example, going to Advanced Settings, going to Hardware and Connection Properties and then finding the MAC address for my Wi-Fi network but it's a lot quicker to simply use getmac in a command prompt to find the MAC Address of various Wi-Fi cards. Now I could use this information within a script as an example so use the command to get to the MAC Address of a specific interface and then change the MAC Address of that interface.",
    "transcript_keywords": [
        "MAC address",
        "Windows computer",
        "MAC",
        "address",
        "find the MAC",
        "WiFi network",
        "VMware Virtual Networks",
        "Windows",
        "network",
        "command",
        "Mac addresses",
        "easily find",
        "Virtual Networks",
        "finding the MAC",
        "WiFi",
        "change the MAC",
        "networks",
        "getmac",
        "Internet Settings",
        "Advanced Settings"
    ],
    "transcript_entity_values": [
        "Network and Internet Settings",
        "Mac",
        "the Wi-Fi",
        "Advanced Settings",
        "Windows",
        "VMware Virtual Networks",
        "2",
        "Hardware and Connection Properties",
        "Wi-Fi",
        "VMware",
        "MAC"
    ],
    "transcript_entity_types": [
        "ORG",
        "PERSON",
        "ORG",
        "WORK_OF_ART",
        "PRODUCT",
        "ORG",
        "CARDINAL",
        "ORG",
        "ORG",
        "ORG",
        "ORG"
    ]
}