{
    "id": "OIxKPptaI1Y",
    "title": "WTF Is A SupaBoy?",
    "channel": "Unbox Therapy",
    "channel_id": "UCsTcErHg8oDvUnTzoqsYeNw",
    "subscriber_count": 24800000,
    "upload_date": "2016-05-10T19:39:26Z",
    "video_url": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OIxKPptaI1Y",
    "category": "Science & Technology",
    "tags": [
        "supaboy",
        "hyperkin",
        "hyperkin supaboy",
        "snes",
        "super nintendo",
        "nintendo",
        "super",
        "pocket",
        "portable",
        "gameboy",
        "unboxtherapy",
        "tech",
        "technology",
        "gaming",
        "video games",
        "retro",
        "games",
        "video",
        "console",
        "xbox",
        "playstation",
        "sony",
        "review",
        "game",
        "unboxing",
        "nes",
        "unbox therapy",
        "video game (industry)",
        "video game",
        "best",
        "mario",
        "gameplay",
        "iphone 6s",
        "apple",
        "iphone",
        "new",
        "samsung",
        "android",
        "smartphone",
        "test",
        "gadgets",
        "funny",
        "top",
        "edge",
        "s7 edge",
        "android (operating system)",
        "apple inc. (publisher)",
        "galaxy",
        "6s",
        "vs",
        "phone",
        "iphone 6",
        "apple iphone",
        "iphone 7"
    ],
    "views": 1646702,
    "likes": 34357,
    "comments_count": 2564,
    "description": "Hyperkin SUPABOY Portable Pocket SNES Console -   FOLLOW ME IN THESE PLACES FOR UPDATES Twitter -  Facebook -  Instagram -  Google Plus -",
    "description_links": [
        "http://amzn.to/1TTsE2G",
        "http://twitter.com/unboxtherapy",
        "http://facebook.com/lewis.hilsenteger",
        "http://instagram.com/unboxtherapy",
        "http://bit.ly/1auEeak"
    ],
    "transcript": "What's up guys, Lew here back with another video. Today We're gonna take a trip down Memory Lane Into the world of Super Nintendo. This is the SupaBoy \"Supa\". Not Super, \"Supa\". SupaBoy. Like the Super Bowl It is Super Nintendo capabilities... In the palm of your hands. It plays actual Super Nintendo cartridges, look at that thing, \"NBA Jam\", are you kidding me? It's made by HyperKin. Taking a look around the box here, what do we got? The SupaBoy plays your favorite SNES games. You can see the button layout there in the corner. And it does have a TV output on it, so if you wanna put it onto a bigger display and connect controllers to it, It works as an actual console as well. Oh my! Look at this! I love that font! You see that font there, Jack? \"Play... Like it's 1991\", one of the greatest years ever, 1991. Hey? It's a great year. Well we're gonna play like it's 1991. Ohh, a little traveling kit? Who-ho-ho-hoa. Oh, this is special. This is really, this is special. Look at- Ohhh, my... Jack, what can you say about that? Yeah! Alright! Power switch on the top, AV out, USB port for powering it up. On the bottom, an LED light, volume control, headphone jack, that's nice! I'm taking this to France, Jack! And as I mentioned, the ability to connect some classic controllers if you prefer, Or, potentially to play two-player! One controller, and has you both looking at the tiny little screen... (Laughter) So this is your AV cable. That little guy there will take you out to these RCAs. A little power brick, and then the battery. A chunky battery... 2200 mA hours. Let's get the party started. Oh! A screwdriver. I know how to do that. I can do that Battery in here That's pretty simple. OhhhHHH! If you never done it before, you don't know, but before you die... Try inserting a cartridge. Seriously. Hoo! No Raptors existed at this point in time. Can you remember which team was the go-to at this point? Ooh. Hardaway Mullin, that's tough to beat. (Laughing) Yeah! It's a three! Oh! (Laughter) It's the classic experience in a handheld package. What a crazy contraption! This is what I love! This is not for everybody, this is not to replace your Xbox One, okay? It's a little bit of fun! Maybe it's... Super Mario World, look at that. Kick it old-school a little bit. That's fun. It's taking me back, I hope it took you back too. Ooooh. Ah ha! Look at that guy. Look at that handsome face right there.",
    "transcript_keywords": [
        "Super Nintendo",
        "Super",
        "Memory Lane",
        "actual Super Nintendo",
        "Super Nintendo cartridges",
        "Super Nintendo capabilities",
        "Lew",
        "plays actual Super",
        "Nintendo",
        "Super Bowl",
        "Lew here back",
        "Jack",
        "Super Mario World",
        "trip down Memory",
        "Supa",
        "Super Mario",
        "SupaBoy",
        "Play",
        "actual Super",
        "NBA Jam"
    ],
    "transcript_entity_values": [
        "Super Nintendo",
        "Memory Lane",
        "2200 mA hours",
        "Lew",
        "HyperKin",
        "Hardaway Mullin",
        "AV",
        "Supa",
        "years",
        "1991",
        "USB",
        "AV",
        "SupaBoy",
        "SNES",
        "Today",
        "jack",
        "Jack",
        "a great year",
        "two",
        "One",
        "the Super Bowl It",
        "three",
        "France",
        "NBA",
        "one",
        "Xbox One"
    ],
    "transcript_entity_types": [
        "ORG",
        "FAC",
        "TIME",
        "PERSON",
        "ORG",
        "PERSON",
        "PRODUCT",
        "PERSON",
        "DATE",
        "DATE",
        "ORG",
        "ORG",
        "PERSON",
        "ORG",
        "DATE",
        "PERSON",
        "PERSON",
        "DATE",
        "CARDINAL",
        "CARDINAL",
        "EVENT",
        "CARDINAL",
        "GPE",
        "ORG",
        "CARDINAL",
        "ORG"
    ]
}