{
    "id": "PWhRz9O3OLY",
    "title": "The Banana Phone Is Back: Nokia 8110 4G Hands-On",
    "channel": "MrMobile [Michael Fisher]",
    "channel_id": "UCSOpcUkE-is7u7c4AkLgqTw",
    "subscriber_count": 1250000,
    "upload_date": "2018-02-25T23:52:22Z",
    "video_url": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PWhRz9O3OLY",
    "category": "Science & Technology",
    "tags": [
        "Nokia 8110 hands-on",
        "nokia 8110 4g review",
        "nokia 8110 4g hands-on",
        "nokia banana phone review",
        "banana phone hands-on",
        "banana phone 2018",
        "nokia banana",
        "mrmobile",
        "mwc 2018"
    ],
    "views": 696419,
    "likes": 11285,
    "comments_count": 737,
    "description": "\"Matrix Phone.\" \"Banana Phone.\" \"Shameless appeal to nostalgia.\" Whatever your preferred nomenclature, Nokia calls it the \"8110 4G.\" It's a modernized revamp of the original Nokia 8110, the mobile phone that first popularized the slider form factor back in 1997. And for sentimental suckers like MrMobile, it's 79 Euros as good as spent. Join me for the Nokia 8110 4G Hands-On!   [SPONSOR]  This video is brought to you by Thrifter, a new way to save money by shopping based on value (and not hype). Visit Thrifter for great deals on everything from gadgets to home goods, at    [SUBSCRIBE]     [ABOUT MRMOBILE'S NOKIA 8110 4G HANDS-ON]  MrMobile's Nokia 8110 4G Hands-On was produced following an hour with a Nokia 8110 4G review device at an HMD Global event at MWC 2018 in Barcelona. Preproduction device running prerelease software.   [MUSIC]  Sensational by Cymatix, available at Premium Beat:    [SOCIALIZE]         [DISCLOSURE]  This post may contain affiliate links. See Mobile Nations' disclosure policy for more details:",
    "description_links": [
        "http://thrifter.com.",
        "https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCSOpcUkE-is7u7c4AkLgqTw?sub_confirmation=1",
        "https://www.premiumbeat.com/royalty_free_music/songs/sensational",
        "http://facebook.com/themrmobile",
        "http://instagram.com/themrmobile",
        "http://twitter.com/themrmobile",
        "https://www.snapchat.com/add/mrmobilesnaps",
        "http://mrmobile.tech",
        "http://www.mobilenations.com/external-links"
    ],
    "transcript": "- [Mr. Mobile] The cellphone that saved The Matrix 20 years ago is back. I'm Mr.Mobile, and this year, at the Mobile World Congress, we're saying hello again to the original Banana Phone. (upbeat electronic music) Just like last year, Nokia and nostalgia go hand in hand. The 8110 4G is a modernized revamp of the original 8110, the phone that first popularized the slider form factor back in 1997. Fun fact, while the iconic prop from the Matrix included a spring-loaded mechanism to pop out the slider, the original 8110 did not. And the new one doesn't either. Still, it's an awful lotta fun to slide the cover down to expose the numeric keypad, which also turns on the display. In a time when voice calls were still king, sliders made talking on cellphones feel more natural to a generation of folks raised on the receiver, and the 8110 went the extra mile with a strong curve to the casing, which gave it its Banana Phone nickname and has been faithfully replicated on the new phone. There's a lot here that would've seemed outrageously futuristic back in '97, like the bright color screen, 4G radios, and a camera rated for a whopping two megapixels. Making all that work is KaiOS, a feature phone platform that can run HTML5 apps, including Facebook, Twitter, and Google Maps. That low profile OS and Snapdragon 205 processor mean Nokia can promise nine hours of talk time and over three weeks of standby. When you do recharge, you'll use micro USB. It's an old port, sir, but it checks out. And you'll also notice a headphone jack for the FM radio. Or if you're a Napster addict, you can load some MP3s into the four gigs of onboard storage. Because of the LTE radio, this phone should actually make some pretty clear calls over a VoLTE, and when you're done schooling your friends with Frasier jokes until they're a bunch of angry beavers mad about you declaring yourself king of the hill, well, you can hang up on them just by closing the sliders, slider. So to get in on another round of Snake this spring, you need to do four things. One, save up 79 euros 'cause that's what it'll cost. Two, retrain your thumbs to text with a numeric keypad, and a kinda mushy one at that. Three, decide whether you want it in traditional black or banana yellow. And four, make sure you live in either Europe or China because those are the initial launch markets. The 8110 4G goes on sale in May. (upbeat electronic music) This video was brought to you by Thrifter. Thrifter is a new way to save money on everything from gadgets to home goods by shopping based on value and not hype. Check out the latest deals at thirfter.com, and tell 'em Mr. Mobile sent ya. (upbeat electronic music) Folks, if you're down in the comments wondering why my voice sounds different, it's because I'm recording in Barcelona at MWC 2018. Follow me at theMrMobile on Instagram for up to the second news, and subscribe here on YouTube for more videos just like this. Until next time, thanks for watching, and stay mobile, my friends.",
    "transcript_keywords": [
        "Mobile World Congress",
        "original Banana Phone",
        "saved The Matrix",
        "World Congress",
        "years ago",
        "Banana Phone",
        "Phone",
        "Banana Phone nickname",
        "Mobile World",
        "Banana",
        "Matrix",
        "original Banana",
        "slider",
        "back",
        "original",
        "year",
        "Mobile",
        "Matrix included",
        "Nokia",
        "cellphone that saved"
    ],
    "transcript_entity_values": [
        "Europe",
        "HTML5",
        "two megapixels",
        "LTE",
        "three weeks",
        "8110 4",
        "Instagram",
        "79 euros",
        "The Matrix",
        "the Mobile World Congress",
        "last year",
        "2018",
        "four",
        "Facebook",
        "USB",
        "VoLTE",
        "Napster",
        "China",
        "Mobile",
        "this year",
        "Three",
        "'97",
        "Google Maps",
        "1997",
        "Frasier",
        "first",
        "One",
        "YouTube",
        "jack",
        "nine hours",
        "4",
        "Snapdragon 205",
        "this spring",
        "Nokia",
        "Barcelona",
        "second",
        "20 years ago",
        "Banana Phone",
        "Thrifter",
        "Two",
        "Twitter",
        "May",
        "Matrix",
        "MWC"
    ],
    "transcript_entity_types": [
        "LOC",
        "ORG",
        "QUANTITY",
        "ORG",
        "DATE",
        "DATE",
        "ORG",
        "MONEY",
        "WORK_OF_ART",
        "ORG",
        "DATE",
        "DATE",
        "CARDINAL",
        "ORG",
        "ORG",
        "ORG",
        "ORG",
        "GPE",
        "PERSON",
        "DATE",
        "CARDINAL",
        "DATE",
        "ORG",
        "DATE",
        "PERSON",
        "ORDINAL",
        "CARDINAL",
        "PERSON",
        "PERSON",
        "TIME",
        "CARDINAL",
        "PRODUCT",
        "DATE",
        "ORG",
        "GPE",
        "ORDINAL",
        "DATE",
        "ORG",
        "PERSON",
        "CARDINAL",
        "ORG",
        "DATE",
        "ORG",
        "ORG"
    ]
}