{
    "id": "rlJG2qeQ1RE",
    "title": "The Best New Tricks in macOS Catalina!",
    "channel": "Snazzy Labs",
    "channel_id": "UCO2x-p9gg9TLKneXlibGR7w",
    "subscriber_count": 1170000,
    "upload_date": "2019-06-12T23:08:16Z",
    "video_url": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rlJG2qeQ1RE",
    "category": "Science & Technology",
    "tags": [
        "snazzy labs",
        "quinn nelson",
        "snazzyq",
        "macOS catalina",
        "Mac OS",
        "macOS",
        "Mac OS X",
        "catalina",
        "high Sierra",
        "Mojave",
        "tips",
        "tricks",
        "apple",
        "Mac",
        "macbook",
        "MacBook tips",
        "macbook tricks",
        "iMac",
        "iMac pro",
        "Mac Pro",
        "terminal",
        "utility",
        "Mac apps",
        "best Mac apps",
        "best Mac tricks",
        "project catalyst",
        "Apple TV",
        "appletv",
        "Apple TV plus",
        "appletv+",
        "notes",
        "reminders",
        "system preferences",
        "iTunes",
        "podcasts",
        "streaming service",
        "iOS apps",
        "iOS on Mac",
        "iPad os",
        "ipados",
        "sidecar",
        "Mac on iPad",
        "iPad on Mac"
    ],
    "views": 323963,
    "likes": 7725,
    "comments_count": 640,
    "description": "At WWDC 2019, Apple announced macOS Catalina. We talk about the best new features. Try AdGuard free today at -  and use coupon code SNAZZY_LABS to save 30% at checkout.  Follow Snazzy Labs on Twitter -  Follow me on Instagram -   macOS Catalina brings a lot of new features like Sidecar, Voice Control accessibility features, and updates to the Notes, Reminders, System Preferences. So long, iTunes! Apple replaces iTunes with Apple Music for Mac along with AppleTV for the upcoming AppleTV+ streaming service and a new Podcasts app built inside of the Project Catalyst framework which brings your favorite iOS apps to Mac this fall!",
    "description_links": [
        "https://agrd.io/snazzy",
        "http://twitter.com/snazzyq",
        "http://instagram.com/snazzyq"
    ],
    "transcript": "At WWDC last week, Apple announced the latest version of MacOS. Catalina! And I'm here to show you some of the... new features that it will bring when it comes out later this fall. This video was sponsored by ADGAURD, for iOS, and Desktop. Block ads, speed up web pages, get rid of junk, and more. Try it now today with the link below for free. If you ask me, the headlining feature of both iPadOS 13 and MacOS Catalina is a new utility called Project Sidecar. Now, you will need an iPad, with an A8 Chip or later. And you will need a MacBook, well basically, or an iMac with basically the 2015 Era or later. Both devices need the ability to encode and decode each EVC on the ASIC or SOC. So that's why they need newer hardware. Although, if you do have an old mac, there is a workaround. You can input this terminal command, and get it to work, although your reliability is not quite as good. It's not as good as an experience. But, it does work. But, again, I said it you could use any iPad with an A8 or later. But where this really comes in clutch is if you have an Apple Pencil. Because if I extend the display, it appears as an AirPlay device on my laptop, I just press iPad Pro, and suddenly, it makes my iPad a secondary display! And, I can drag windows over here, just like I would a secondary monitor. I have it set up Right to Left right now, but see that? And you can tell that the latency is really, really good. Ah, but what you can also do, is mirror the display. And it makes your main Mac look a little bit funny, admittedly. But, what it allows you to do, it basically have your entire Mac here on the iPad. And again, latency is excellent! You can control this, with the Touch Pad, if you want. Or you can control it with the Apple Pencil! Now, it doesn't support, touch input. So if you touch stuff, it WILL NOT WORK. I don't-- the Sinicon believes it's because Apple wants you to buy a $130 Apple Pencil and a new iPad Pro. Realistically, it's probably because, they haven't really optimized MacOS for these smaller displays, so the touch targets are very small, and your fat fingers may not be able to do that. If you do have, and iPad. however, you can emulate the Touch Bar! So down here,",
    "transcript_keywords": [
        "WWDC last week",
        "announced the latest",
        "latest version",
        "Apple Pencil",
        "Apple",
        "WWDC",
        "Apple announced",
        "iPad",
        "Touch",
        "iPad Pro",
        "Pencil",
        "work",
        "mac",
        "display",
        "MacOS",
        "Project Sidecar",
        "good",
        "week",
        "Catalina",
        "Pro"
    ],
    "transcript_entity_values": [
        "13",
        "the Touch Bar!",
        "EVC",
        "Apple",
        "A8",
        "SOC",
        "iPad Pro",
        "AirPlay",
        "Catalina",
        "Mac",
        "iPad",
        "iPad",
        "the Touch Pad",
        "today",
        "the Apple Pencil!",
        "Apple Pencil",
        "Sinicon",
        "ADGAURD",
        "$130",
        "later this fall",
        "Project Sidecar",
        "iMac",
        "last week",
        "MacOS",
        "an A8 Chip",
        "MacOS Catalina",
        "ASIC",
        "MacBook"
    ],
    "transcript_entity_types": [
        "CARDINAL",
        "ORG",
        "ORG",
        "ORG",
        "PRODUCT",
        "ORG",
        "PRODUCT",
        "PRODUCT",
        "ORG",
        "PERSON",
        "ORG",
        "PRODUCT",
        "ORG",
        "DATE",
        "ORG",
        "ORG",
        "PERSON",
        "ORG",
        "MONEY",
        "DATE",
        "ORG",
        "ORG",
        "DATE",
        "ORG",
        "PRODUCT",
        "ORG",
        "ORG",
        "FAC"
    ]
}