{
    "id": "vI25nMmklwE",
    "title": "Make Coca-Cola At Home?",
    "channel": "Unbox Therapy",
    "channel_id": "UCsTcErHg8oDvUnTzoqsYeNw",
    "subscriber_count": 24800000,
    "upload_date": "2015-11-25T02:26:24Z",
    "video_url": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vI25nMmklwE",
    "category": "Science & Technology",
    "tags": [
        "keurig",
        "keurig kold",
        "kold",
        "cold",
        "coke",
        "coca-cola",
        "Cola (Beverage)",
        "Coca",
        "soda",
        "soda stream",
        "review",
        "keurig kold review",
        "unboxing",
        "unboxtherapy",
        "unbox therapy",
        "tech",
        "technology",
        "soft drink (beverage type)",
        "coca-cola (endorsed product)",
        "sodastream",
        "coca cola",
        "pop",
        "make soda",
        "sodastream (business operation)",
        "keurig kold vs sodastream",
        "keurig kold pods",
        "home soda maker",
        "flavored soda",
        "keurig review",
        "make soda at home",
        "sparkling water",
        "make a coke at home",
        "taste test",
        "soda maker"
    ],
    "views": 13122878,
    "likes": 292732,
    "comments_count": 12640,
    "description": "Keurig Kold -   FOLLOW ME IN THESE PLACES FOR UPDATES Twitter -  Facebook -  Instagram -  Google Plus -",
    "description_links": [
        "http://www.keurig.ca/kold",
        "http://twitter.com/unboxtherapy",
        "http://facebook.com/lewis.hilsenteger",
        "http://instagram.com/unboxtherapy",
        "http://bit.ly/1auEeak"
    ],
    "transcript": "What's up guys Lew here back with another video and today I have something that I am really pumped up for I don't normally say pumped up that's kinda new. Me and Jack have been talking about this thing since it arrived We have a serious problem here at the office with keeping cold beverages or actually any kind of edible material for very long. We consume it. This thing here is like a solution to all of our problems All the problems in our lives. Keurig has asked me to check out their brand new KOLD. Keurig KOLD A variety of your favorite beverages made in this machine right at home in a little pod And it's licensed! You have Coca-cola products in here. Concept is you have a little pod. We see a picture of it there Stick it in the machine. Hit the button. Boo-ya? Cold beverage? Let's jump inside the box and find out if that's exactly what goes down First thing I see here: A prime and care pod. Do not discard. Required for setup and maintenance. Okay. Coca-cola, Sprite, Red Barn, Waterful Looks like a little tray for the bottom. So this is it. This is the Keurig Kold. Now it has a refrigeration unit built in So this is the reservoir for water. Ohhh! This is glasses Drink maker chills beverages to an ideal temperature of 39 degrees farenheit This whole thing feels pretty robust man. Plug her in and let her go. Alright we're gonna plug her in Plug it in So I think you guys can probably hear that As I've said sort of around the same volume as a mini fridge. So we left it for a little while and we're actually not going to have to do that again That's just the initial setup. And now it's time to prime it There's a little thing here called a Prime and Care Pod. Fill the water reservoir with room temperature or cooler water That's what we have in here right now. It's filled up. Insert the Prime and Care Pod Put it right in here I guess Done. Place a glass here on the drip tray. So we have the included glasses here Alright let's go here. This is exciting K next up make a drink. This is what it's about right now! Ok Seraphine Passion Fruit. Natural Flavor seltzer mix. \"Lifts you to a place of breezy effervescence\" What a combination of words there. No calories, low calories, zero calories Zero calorie flavored water.The classic Coca-Cola at home. Seems impossible It's happening here! What! Look at his thing! Ohh this looks fancy too. Flynn's soda shop root beer. Mmmmmm What! Diet coke too! Course you do! This is another flavored carbonated water This is one is persian lime. Flyte \"Red Rush\". Natural fruit punch flavored sports hydration mix It's time to do a taste test. Oh my goodness the pressure is on The pressure is on right now. So I'm gonna get started with one of these. Sarafine Persian Lime pods. Just place this guy in. Close the lid down. Now let's push this button for the magic part You see that carbonation right now. Look at that oooo! Quite refreshing. Gotta be honest quite refreshing! A little bit nicer than a standard water beverage. So I believe these little beads inside are what allow for the carbonation to be added to the flavor Next up I have Zero Calorie flavored water so this is a non carbonated-similar idea but non carbonated Mmm! You came here for the OG of the soda business. You came here for the Coca-Cola Classic Everything hinges on this little guy right here The future is now Don't laugh Jack. Ooouuuuhhhhhh ho ho ho hoooo That looks like Coca Cola That is Coca Cola Gotta bite. Gotta little bite to it. I don't think I've ever been this excited for Coke in my life. ( ) So there you have it. Keurig Kold Thank you very much for watching. If you've enjoyed this content make sure to leave a thumbs up down below. Subscribe if you haven't yet. and I will catch you on the next episode. Now I will drink my Coke. Slowly and dramatically",
    "transcript_keywords": [
        "Lew here back",
        "guys Lew",
        "video and today",
        "care pod",
        "Keurig KOLD",
        "pumped",
        "water",
        "Lew",
        "pod",
        "thing",
        "prime and care",
        "KOLD",
        "prime",
        "Care Pod Put",
        "Keurig",
        "calorie flavored water",
        "Cocacola",
        "kind",
        "care",
        "Coca Cola"
    ],
    "transcript_entity_values": [
        "Lew",
        "Keurig KOLD",
        "Care Pod",
        "persian",
        "Coca Cola",
        "Ooouuuuhhhhhh ho ho ho hoooo",
        "Flynn",
        "Sarafine",
        "Coca-cola",
        "Stick",
        "the Coca-Cola Classic",
        "First",
        "Ok Seraphine Passion Fruit",
        "Persian",
        "Keurig Kold",
        "Jack",
        "Coca Cola Gotta",
        "Coca-Cola",
        "Sprite",
        "Coke",
        "Flyte",
        "zero",
        "KOLD",
        "Keurig",
        "the Keurig Kold",
        "Care Pod Put",
        "Diet coke",
        "39 degrees farenheit",
        "Zero",
        "one",
        "Boo-ya"
    ],
    "transcript_entity_types": [
        "PERSON",
        "PERSON",
        "ORG",
        "NORP",
        "ORG",
        "PERSON",
        "PERSON",
        "NORP",
        "ORG",
        "FAC",
        "ORG",
        "ORDINAL",
        "ORG",
        "NORP",
        "PERSON",
        "PERSON",
        "ORG",
        "ORG",
        "ORG",
        "ORG",
        "ORG",
        "CARDINAL",
        "ORG",
        "ORG",
        "ORG",
        "WORK_OF_ART",
        "PRODUCT",
        "QUANTITY",
        "CARDINAL",
        "CARDINAL",
        "PERSON"
    ]
}