{
    "id": "Vin6JIDyZrE",
    "title": "The BEST Operating System for Raspberry Pi 5? #shorts #raspberrypi5 #kalilinux",
    "channel": "David Bombal",
    "channel_id": "UCP7WmQ_U4GB3K51Od9QvM0w",
    "subscriber_count": 2650000,
    "upload_date": "2023-11-04T14:30:11Z",
    "video_url": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Vin6JIDyZrE",
    "category": "Science & Technology",
    "tags": [
        "linux",
        "kali linux",
        "kali",
        "raspberry pi 5",
        "raspberrypi5",
        "raspberry pi",
        "raspberry pi 4",
        "wifi",
        "wi-fi",
        "pi 5",
        "pi5",
        "raspberry pi5",
        "wpa2",
        "wpa3",
        "wpa",
        "raspberry 5",
        "pi 5 vs pi 4",
        "wifi password",
        "password",
        "wireless",
        "ssid",
        "find wifi password",
        "wlan",
        "wifi hacking",
        "cybersecurity",
        "hacking",
        "ethical hacking",
        "hacker",
        "wpa2 cracking",
        "wifi password hacker",
        "wpa2 hacking",
        "wifi cracking",
        "hack",
        "wifi gadget",
        "md5",
        "password cracking",
        "password crack",
        "md5 password",
        "sha",
        "sha1",
        "sha256",
        "sha512",
        "kali linux raspberry pi"
    ],
    "views": 558027,
    "likes": 23825,
    "comments_count": 179,
    "description": "Please note that I was not paid for this video. Raspberry Pi did send me a free Raspberry Pi 5 for me to test with.  Watch this video to learn more:   #raspberrypi5 #kalilinux #linux",
    "description_links": [
        "https://youtu.be/paN5F1EmjfA"
    ],
    "transcript": "This is a Raspberry Pi 5 and on this SD card is one of my favorite Operating Systems, let's insert that into the Pi connect the Pi to OBS running on that laptop, plug it in my mouse and keyboard let's power this on Rasberry Pi is now starting the fan is spinning and as you can see there starting to boot up and what do you know there's Kali Linux running on a Raspberry Pi 5. Default username and password is kali kali open up a terminal as you can see here it's kali@kali-raspberry-pi-5 lsb_release -a you can see that we're running 2023.3 Kalii Linux on a Raspberry Pi iwconfig shows that I have a Wi-Fi adapter Raspberry Pi 5 has a built-in Wi-Fi adapter you can see that the network I'm connected to is free Wi-Fi and I can ping google.com from this Raspberry Pi 5 fantastic to see that Kalii Linux is now available on a Raspberry Pi 5.",
    "transcript_keywords": [
        "favorite Operating Systems",
        "Operating Systems",
        "Kali Linux running",
        "favorite Operating",
        "WiFi adapter Raspberry",
        "kali kali open",
        "Kalii Linux",
        "Raspberry",
        "OBS running",
        "mouse and keyboard",
        "fan is spinning",
        "Linux running",
        "kali kali",
        "adapter Raspberry",
        "Raspberry Pi iwconfig",
        "Linux",
        "Kali",
        "starting the fan",
        "starting to boot",
        "builtin WiFi adapter"
    ],
    "transcript_entity_values": [
        "Operating Systems",
        "SD",
        "Kalii Linux",
        "Kali Linux",
        "kali kali",
        "2023.3",
        "this Raspberry Pi 5",
        "Raspberry Pi",
        "Wi-Fi",
        "OBS",
        "Rasberry Pi"
    ],
    "transcript_entity_types": [
        "ORG",
        "ORG",
        "PERSON",
        "PERSON",
        "PERSON",
        "CARDINAL",
        "ORG",
        "ORG",
        "LOC",
        "ORG",
        "PERSON"
    ]
}