{
    "id": "Y7zS-ZICkWk",
    "title": "The OnePlus 7 looks SO CLEAN",
    "channel": "Dave2D",
    "channel_id": "UCVYamHliCI9rw1tHR1xbkfw",
    "subscriber_count": 3660000,
    "upload_date": "2019-01-22T18:41:17Z",
    "video_url": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Y7zS-ZICkWk",
    "category": "Science & Technology",
    "tags": [
        "Dave2D",
        "Review",
        "oneplus 7",
        "one plus 7",
        "bezel less phone",
        "no notch phone",
        "phone without notch",
        "notched phone",
        "best phone",
        "best smartphone",
        "best phones 2019",
        "best smartphone 2019",
        "best budget phones 2019",
        "best cheap phone 2019"
    ],
    "views": 2454208,
    "likes": 45648,
    "comments_count": 4238,
    "description": "An early look at the OnePlus 7 based on leaks. Super excited for this phone - I think it'll be the best looking phone OnePlus has ever put out. OP6T -   Background Music Fili - Sunday Vibes  If you want to support the channel, consider a Dave2D membership by clicking the Join button above!      Purchases made from store links may give me some money.  (It doesnt cost you extra, so please buy everything)",
    "description_links": [
        "https://amzn.to/2CztHRP",
        "http://twitter.com/Dave2D",
        "http://www.instagram.com/Dave2D",
        "https://discord.gg/Dave2D"
    ],
    "transcript": "Hey, How's it going? Dave 2D here So the other day, a photo was leaked on SlashLeaks that looks to be the upcoming OnePlus 7. And this is a photo that speaks volumes on what this phone is going to look like. If it's accurate it's going to be a phone with no notches, no cameras, nothing on the front screen. It's going to be a thinly bezelled phone and it's going to look super clean Now, we've seen other notchless phones from other companies before, right like Vevo, Huawei, Xiaomi, and even Lenovo. They all have these notch-less camera-less designs that look good but this might be the first notch-less and obstruction free display phone that we see readily available in North America. So it will work with Verizon and stuff like that. And the way that they have done this; the way that they have achieved this look is through a sliding mechanism.",
    "transcript_keywords": [
        "Hey",
        "phone",
        "North America",
        "notchless",
        "photo",
        "upcoming OnePlus",
        "leaked on SlashLeaks",
        "Huawei",
        "Xiaomi",
        "Vevo",
        "Lenovo",
        "America",
        "work with Verizon",
        "Verizon and stuff",
        "notchless phones",
        "North",
        "photo was leaked",
        "Dave",
        "day",
        "OnePlus"
    ],
    "transcript_entity_values": [
        "North America",
        "Verizon",
        "Vevo",
        "Huawei",
        "Xiaomi",
        "OnePlus 7",
        "Lenovo",
        "Dave",
        "first",
        "SlashLeaks",
        "the other day"
    ],
    "transcript_entity_types": [
        "LOC",
        "ORG",
        "ORG",
        "ORG",
        "PERSON",
        "EVENT",
        "ORG",
        "PERSON",
        "ORDINAL",
        "ORG",
        "DATE"
    ]
}